Contact

(650) 666-5277 (Mobile) lin.kungmin@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kungminlin (LinkedIn)

github.com/kungminlin (Other) www.facebook.com/lin.kungmin (Other)

Top Skills

Python

Web Development

Natural Language Processing (NLP)

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Chinese (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

AP Scholar with Honor Award

FBLA Spreadsheet Applications - 6th Place in Sectionals

FBLA Spreadsheet Applications - 5th Place in States, National Qualifier

2019 FRC Ventura Regional Finalist Award

2019 FRC Ventura Regional Innovation in Control Award

Kung-Min Lin

Lead and Sponsorship Director at Los Altos Hacks

Mountain View, California

Summary

I am a high school student who is highly interested in data processing and software engineering. Although I have more practical skills when it comes to front-end and back-end web development, I have studied a lot about machine learning algorithms and their underlying mathematical concepts. I have an understanding of business through my experience in FBLA. This experience, when combined with my work at Los Altos Hacks, LingHacks, and other organizations, help promote my leadership and outreach skills.

Experience

University of California, Riverside Research Assistant June 2019 - Present

Riverside, CA

ESCAL (Extreme Storage and Computer Architecture Lab)

- o Project OpenUVR
- o Simulating Posture and Head Movement with MATLAB, Adafruit LSM9DS Triple-Axis Sensor, and VisionHMD
- o Adapting Head Movement Analysis from Gait Tracking Modules developed by x-io Technologies

Hack Club
President
April 2019 - Present
Los Altos, California

Los Altos Hacks Lead and Sponsorship Director April 2019 - Present California

2019 - 2020 (Los Altos Hacks V)

LingHacks

Curriculum Developer August 2018 - Present

California

- o Designs NLP curriculum for high school students in the Bay Area and prepare workshop materials for the LingHacks Hackathon.
- o Finds sponsors for the hackathon. (LingHacks)
- o Helps host workshops and lectures on NLP.

FRC Team 114, Eagle Strike - FIRST Robotics Competition CAD Designer and Programmer

August 2018 - Present

United States

- o FRC Deep Space 2019 World Championship
- o CAD Design with Solidworks
- o NASA OpenMCT Dashboard Integration
- o Rust and NodeJS

SRND

Organizer

December 2018 - Present

San Francisco Bay Area

CodeDay Bay Area

- o Outreach Coordinating
- o Social Media Management

Hack Club

Secretary

August 2018 - April 2019 (9 months)

Los Altos, California

LAHS Hack Club

- o Manages get.lahs.club program, helping clubs and organizations in Los Altos High School spread their initiatives through websites
- o Teaches an intermediate group full-stack development basics and NodeJS implementation with Express and MongoDB (MERN-Stack)
- o Teaches an intermediate group basic concepts of machine learning, including core mathematical/computational principles and implementation in Python. Covers NLP, RNN, and CNN.

Los Altos Hacks

Organizer

June 2017 - April 2019 (1 year 11 months)

California

2017 - 2018 (Los Altos Hacks III)

o Outreach Coordinator: Reaching out to high school college and career centers as well as teachers to advertise the event.

o Sponsorship Coordinator: Finding and coordinating sponsors

2018 - 2019 (Los Altos Hacks IV)

o Outreach Coordinator: Reaching out to high school students from all over the Bay Area

o Sponsorship Coordinator: Finding and coordinating sponsors

o Technical Coordinator: Developing tech gadgets and applications for a more immersive hackathon experience

o Graphics Designer: Made posters and social media graphics for promotional purposes.

Rising Star Magazine Staff Editor August 2018 - December 2018 (5 months) United States

Writes articles for the environmental column - mainly focusing on the topic of intersection between technology and environmental protection.

VMware

High School Immersion Program August 2018 - August 2018 (1 month)

United States

I participated in a high school immersion program hosted by VMware, which included activities such as workshops with software developers and a presentation from the CEO. Over the course of three days, we not only learned about the working environment in VMware, but also the general workflow adopted by professionals in software development.

Education

Los Altos High School
High School Diploma, Computer Science · (2016 - 2020)

Foothill College

Mathematics and Computer Science · (2018 - 2019)